A 104 -year -old woman is selling the house she has lived in since she was two years
old. Nancy Gifford was born months after the end of the First World War.
And spent 102 years living in her three -bedroom house in the Somerset village of
Street. And spent 102 years living in her three -bedroom house in the Somerset
village of And spent 102 years living in her three -bedroom house in the Somerset
village of Street.
She is now putting it on the market, having lived in it through the Second World War
and the invention of television.
She is now putting it on the market,
having lived in it through the Second World War and the invention of television.
Her family bought the house for £200 in 1921 and it is now priced at some £170,000.
According to the Bank of England's calculator, £200 in 1921 would be worth £7,750
today. According to the Bank of England's calculator, £200 in 1921 would be worth £7
,750 today. According to the Bank of England's inflation calculator, £200 in 1921
would be worth £7,750 today.
According to the estate agent, the house was built in 1882 and originally featured a
well for the entire road.
to the estate agent, the house was built in 1882 and